wearethecity.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy – WeAreTheCity – Work With Us

This privacy policy applies between you, the User of this Website and We Are The City Limited, the owner and provider of this Website. We Are The City Limited takes the privacy of your information very seriously. This privacy policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us or provided by you in relation to your use of the Website.

**Please read this privacy policy carefully**.

#### Definitions and interpretation

 1\. In this privacy policy, the following definitions are used:

**Data** | collectively all information that you submit to We Are The City Limited via the Website. This definition incorporates, where applicable, the definitions provided in the Data Protection Act 1998;  
---|---  
**Cookies** | a small text file placed on your computer by this Website when you visit certain parts of the Website and/or when you use certain features of the Website. Details of the cookies used by this Website are set out in the clause below ( **Cookies** );  
**We Are The City Limited,** or **us** | We Are The City Limited, a company incorporated in England and Wales with registered number 6369225 whose registered office is at Suite 2, 44-50 High Street, Rayleigh, Essex, SS6 7EA  
**UK and EU Cookie Law** | the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 as amended by the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) (Amendment) Regulations 2011;  
**User** or **you** | any third party that accesses the Website and is not either (i) employed by We Are The City Limited and acting in the course of their employment or (ii) engaged as a consultant or otherwise providing services to We Are The City Limited and accessing the Website in connection with the provision of such services; and  
**Website** | the website that you are currently using, wearethecity.com, and or wearethecityjobs.com, gendernetworks.com, careersclub.wearethecity.com, jobs.wearethecity.in, wearefutureleaders.wearethecity.com, wearetechwomen.wearethecity.com, workwithus.wearethecity.com and or wearethecity.in  and any sub-domains of this site unless expressly excluded by their own terms and conditions.  
  
 2\. In this privacy policy, unless the context requires a different interpretation:

 a. the singular includes the plural and vice versa;

 b. references to sub-clauses, clauses, schedules or appendices are to sub-clauses, clauses, schedules or appendices of this privacy policy;

 c. a reference to a person includes firms, companies, government entities, trusts and partnerships;

 d. “including” is understood to mean “including without limitation”;

 e. reference to any statutory provision includes any modification or amendment of it;

 f. the headings and sub-headings do not form part of this privacy policy.

#### Scope of this privacy policy

 3\. This privacy policy applies only to the actions of We Are The City Limited and Users with respect to this Website. It does not extend to any websites that can be accessed from this Website including, but not limited to, any links we may provide to social media websites.

#### Data collected

4.  Information you give to us.

  * We will use this information:
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, that you require from our website;
  * to provide you with information about other services we offer that are similar to those subscribed for or enquired about;
  * to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. If you are an existing member, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you. ;
  * to notify you about changes to our service;
  * to refer your experiences, skills and preferences to other users of our website in order to match you with appropriate individuals from different organisations who are registered on our website;
  * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

4.1. Information we collect about you.

  * We will use this information:
  * to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
  * to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  * as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;
  * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
  * to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.

#### Our use of Data

 5\. For purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, We Are The City Limited is the “data controller”.

 6\. We will retain any Data you submit for 2 months.

 7\. Unless we are obliged or permitted by law to do so, and subject to any third party disclosures specifically set out in this policy, your Data will not be disclosed to third parties. This includes our affiliates and / or other companies within our group.

 8\. All personal Data is stored securely in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998. For more details on security see the clause below ( **Security** ).

 9\. Any or all of the above Data may be required by us from time to time in order to provide you with the best possible service and experience when using our Website. Specifically, Data may be used by us for the following reasons:

 a. internal record keeping;

 b. improvement of our products / services;

 c. transmission by email of promotional materials that may be of interest to you;

 d. contact for market research purposes which may be done using email, telephone, fax or mail. Such information may be used to customise or update the Website;

in each case, in accordance with this privacy policy.

#### Third party websites and services

 10\. We Are The City Limited may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with certain processes necessary for the operation of the Website. The providers of such services do not have access to certain personal Data provided by Users of this Website.

#### Links to other websites

 11\. This Website may, from time to time, provide links to other websites. We have no control over such websites and are not responsible for the content of these websites. This privacy policy does not extend to your use of such websites. You are advised to read the privacy policy or statement of other websites prior to using them.

#### Changes of business ownership and control

 12\. We Are The City Limited may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale and/or the transfer of control of all or part of We Are The City Limited. Data provided by Users will, where it is relevant to any part of our business so transferred, be transferred along with that part and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this privacy policy, be permitted to use the Data for the purposes for which it was originally supplied to us.

 13\. We may also disclose Data to a prospective purchaser of our business or any part of it.

 14\. In the above instances, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring your privacy is protected.

#### Controlling use of your Data

 15\. Wherever you are required to submit Data, you will be given options to restrict our use of that Data. This may include the following:

 16\. use of Data for direct marketing purposes; and

 17\. sharing Data with third parties.

#### Functionality of the Website

 18\. To use all features and functions available on the Website, you may be required to submit certain Data.

 19\. You may restrict your internet browser’s use of Cookies. For more information see the clause below ( **Cookies** ).

#### Accessing your own Data

 20\. You have the right to ask for a copy of any of your personal Data held by We Are The City Limited (where such Data is held).

20.1  The Act gives  you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request can be requested via info@wearethecity.com

#### Security

 21\. Data security is of great importance to We Are The City Limited and to protect your Data we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure Data collected via this Website.

 22\. If password access is required for certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.

 23\. We endeavour to do our best to protect your personal Data. However, transmission of information over the internet is not entirely secure and is done at your own risk. We cannot ensure the security of your Data transmitted to the Website.

#### Cookies

 24\. This Website may place and access certain Cookies on your computer. We Are The City Limited uses Cookies to improve your experience of using the Website and to improve our range of products and services. We Are The City Limited has carefully chosen these Cookies and has taken steps to ensure that your privacy is protected and respected at all times.

 25\. All Cookies used by this Website are used in accordance with current UK and EU Cookie Law.

 26\. Before the Website places Cookies on your computer, you will be presented with a message bar requesting your consent to set those Cookies. By giving your consent to the placing of Cookies, you are enabling We Are The City Limited to provide a better experience and service to you. You may, if you wish, deny consent to the placing of Cookies; however certain features of the Website may not function fully or as intended.

 27\. This Website may place the following Cookies:

 28\. **Type of Cookie Purpose** Analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.Functionality cookies. These are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).

 29\. You can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your internet browser. By default, most internet browsers accept Cookies but this can be changed. For further details, please consult the help menu in your internet browser.

 30\. You can choose to delete Cookies at any time; however you may lose any information that enables you to access the Website more quickly and efficiently including, but not limited to, personalisation settings.

 31\. It is recommended that you ensure that your internet browser is up-to-date and that you consult the help and guidance provided by the developer of your internet browser if you are unsure about adjusting your privacy settings.

#### Transfers outside the European Economic Area

32\. The data that we collect from you will be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (”EEA”). It will also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. This includes staff engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Edit Development Ltd will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

33\. If we transfer Data outside the EEA in this way, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this privacy policy. You expressly agree to such transfers of Data.

#### General

34\. You may not transfer any of your rights under this privacy policy to any other person. We may transfer our rights under this privacy policy where we reasonably believe your rights will not be affected.

 35\. If any court or competent authority finds that any provision of this privacy policy (or part of any provision) is invalid, illegal or unenforceable, that provision or part-provision will, to the extent required, be deemed to be deleted, and the validity and enforceability of the other provisions of this privacy policy will not be affected.

 36\. Unless otherwise agreed, no delay, act or omission by a party in exercising any right or remedy will be deemed a waiver of that, or any other, right or remedy.

 37\. This privacy policy is governed by and interpreted according to English law. All disputes arising under this privacy policy are subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts.

 38\. Our WeAreTheCity Job sites (wearethecityjobs.com and jobs.wearethecity.in) has the ability to apply for jobs via Facebook and Linkedin for candidate convenience. The information provided during the application process will not be shared or used for any other purpose by We Are The City Limited or its recruiting partners. By applying for a job via social media (Facebook, Linkedin) you are agreeing to the purpose and use of your profile for applying to a job advertisement.

#### Your Rights

39\. You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [info@wearethecity.com](mailto:info@wearethecity.com)

40\. Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

#### Changes to this privacy policy

 41\. We Are The City Limited  reserves the right to change this privacy policy as we may deem necessary from time to time or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on the Website and you are deemed to have accepted the terms of the privacy policy on your first use of the Website following the alterations.

You may contact We Are The City Limited by email at [info@wearethecity.com](mailto:info@wearethecity.com).

**Updated 03 February 2018**

**Updated 07 November 2016  
**
